Nobita's Wedding Ceremony?!
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
It was you, Princess Snow White, whom I've been waiting for, all these years....
You are the prince from my dreams. I can't believe that you're right in front of me!
Ah! Oh no!
You two are holding hands of each other and flirting, I can't watch it anymore...
You two are still in primary school.
And yet....
Shizuka-chan, you dummy!
Why is he so upset, I wonder?
But we were just rehearsing the script of Snow White...
Shizuka-chan will...
Dekisugi will beat me to it!
Hey, Nobita-kun!
He's good in sports too.
So Shizuka-chan and Dekisugi-kun were holding each others' hands and flirting?
Right. He might have already proposed marriage to her!
How nonsensical.
Doraemon, you should talk...
Nobita-kun's worry is building up, once again.
Didn't we already visit Shizuka-chan of, 25 years from now, in the future?
Note: See the story "Nobita's Wife-To-Be"
Sure, she was my wife then.
Then no worries.
But you're only here so that I can have a bright future?
Yep, but....
Maybe I was unable to marry Shizuka-chan...
But, what can I do....?
If you are so worried... Then, why don't we visit your Wedding Ceremony?
Time Note!
Let's see...
Nobita-kun's Wedding Ceremony is on...
Wait, what if I marry someone else...?
But you're so unpopular with other girls!
No way!
On a sunny day... 12 years from now....
The wedding reception is being held at the Prince Melon Hotel.
Doraemon!
Well, are you coming with me or not?
I'm coming, of course!
The site where our house had stood then, had been now turned into a public toilet...
Prince Melon Hotel is over there!
Prince Melon Hotel
Here we are.
Let's go and watch what happens!
But wait...
I'm so anxious.
Well, sure you are...
Don't say that...
He's the Future Me.
But he ran in such a hurry...
He must have been late, probably.
On what floor is the ceremony taking place?
Of mister whom, may I ask?
Nobi Nobita and Minamoto Shizuka.
Yay!
Just a moment please...
Hey, did you hear that?
"Nobi Nobita and Minamoto Shizuka" he says...
Aren't you happy?
I'm going to marry Shizuka-chan...
Dekisugi ain't got a thing on me!
But you came a day earlier than the scheduled day.
He got the date wrong.
Nobita-kun, you never grew up, seriously.
But wait, if the ceremony is tomorrow, then why are we here today?
I must have pressed the wrong button of the Time Machine...
Oh well.
Now that we are sure that I'm gonna marry Shizuka-chan...
Since we're already here, let's visit the ceremony tomorrow.
I'm home!
We're living in a big mansion like this, huh?
You rose early and went in a hurry, but where did you went to?
I'd went to view the ceremony hall...
"I'd went in taxi to view the ceremony hall..." he says...!
He's not tired at all.
But time sure flies so fast, he was so childish always.
Indeed.
He's gonna get married tomorrow.
I'm so happy.
But will Nobita be OK after marriage?
I'm also worried about that.
Well, I'm your child after all...
Your parents care for you like you're still a child.
Oh, right! Nobita!
What, mum?
There was a call from Gouda Takeshi-san.
I had forgot. We planned to conduct rehearsal for tomorrow.
Gouda Store
Giant's home is still the same.,.
Our beloved idol, Shizuka-chan...
You're gonna make her yours!
I envy you, buddy.
Ouch.. It hurts...
He looks so happy!
They're just chillin' out!
Make sure to maker her happy, Nobita-kun...
I will, of course...
I'll pulverize you, if you maker her cry...
Yes, I will take good care of her...
I'm so tearful.
It's midnight already!
The full-moon is beautiful as ever.
I wonder what Shizuka-chan is up to...
The trio are having a farewell party, it seems...
Ah! It's Shizuka-chan. She's as beautiful as ever.
I will wash the rest! Go to sleep now!
But...
You need to rise early, tomorrow, so...
Oh, and don't forget to say good night to your father.
Yes, I will.
Yes?
Good night, Daddy!
Wish you good night!
Good night!
That's it? She's going to be married tomorrow and go away...
She just can't be honest at a time like this.
Let's use "Truth Transmitter!"
Daddy, I won't marry anyone.
WHAT?!
Why are you saying so?
If I'm gone, won't you become lonely, daddy?
But of course!
I regret that I wasn't able to do anything for you two in return.
Not really! It's been very lively for us ever since you were born.
The memories you shared with us are like precious gifts for us.
As long as our memories last, I feel like I can handle the loneliness.
So you don't need to worry about me, Shizuka.
You should be able to realize the happiness by marrying Nobita-kun and starting a family.
Your decision to marry Nobita-kun was right, I'm sure of that.
He wishes for others' happiness and shares their sorrows as if it were his own.
I believe that's most important thing about a person.
Shizuka-chan!
I promise I'll make you happy!
Just you wait and see!
I promise, I will! I mean it....!
So please believe me!